Ooh! Look who's out on a date. Pasadena's
favorite power couple, Shamy.
(Sheldon:)And that is the answer
to the question:
"What is wrong with
eating at the Cheesecake Factory?"
(Penny:)So are we celebrating
anything special tonight?
(Amy:)Oh, yes.
(Amy:)Our relationship agreement specifies
the second Thursday of every month...
(Amy:)...or the third Thursday in a month
with five Thursdays is date night.
(Penny:)That is so hot.
(Sheldon:)All right, without objection,
the minutes of the previous date...
(Sheldon:)...are considered read
and agreed to. Any new business?
- How was your day?
- Superb.
(Sheldon:)This morning I made
a palindrome with my Alpha-Bits.
"Nice Hat, Bob Tahecin."
(Amy:)Sounds like you hit the ground running.
I have a bit of good news myseIf.
(Amy:)My most recent paper on how
cooperative long-term potentiation...